<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Christian Levers Research</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Christian Levers Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Christian Levers</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Balancing land-based production with socio-environmental sustainability</title>
      <link>/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/hero/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography I am a Marie Skłodowska-Curie Actions Global Fellow at the Department of Computational Landscape Ecology (Helmholtz Centre for Environmental Research - UFZ) and the Institute for Resources, Environment, and Sustainability (University of British Columbia) as well as a UBC Killam Postdoctoral Research Fellow at the School of Public Policy and Global Affairs (University of British Columbia).
I was trained as a physical geographer and obtained my Bachelor degree at the Ruhr-Universität Bochum (Germany) in 2006 and my Master degree at Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin (Germany) in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>You can find a full list of my publications here.
You can also check out my research contributions on GoogleScholar, ORCID, or ResearcherID (L-9204-2013).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching &amp; Supervision</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Full-term courses taught as the principal or co-lecturer (marked in bold) were evaluated consistently above average Thesis supervision  1 &amp;ndash; Pötzschner, F (2016). Post-release movement pattern analysis of a brown bear in the Lesser Caucasus. Bachelor thesis, Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany.  Graduate level  2016: Invited lecture and seminar on spatial modelling and spatial statistics (IAMO Doctorate Programme, Halle, Germany, 8 h) 2012 – 2014: Invited lecture and seminar on spatial statistics and ESDA (IAMO Doctorate Programme, Halle, Germany, 3 h)  Master level  2014 – 2018: Quantitative methods (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, final exam project supervision, winter term) 2014 – 2016: Ecosystem Services and Biodiversity - seminar on spatial clustering techniques (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 3h, summer term) 2012 &amp;amp; 2014: Land System Science - seminar on land use intensity (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 3 h, winter term) 2011: Land System Science - literature seminar on land use change processes, impacts, drivers, and actors (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 3 h, winter term) 2009: Advanced methods of Geoinformation processing (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 32 h, winter term) 2009: Advanced methods of Geoinformation processing (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, substitute lecture on spatial modelling and spatial analysis, 6 h, winter term) 2009: Mathematics for Geographers (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, lecture and seminar, 6 h, winter term)  Bachelor level  2018: Project seminar Carpathians - field trip (1 week) and 2 seminars (8h) on data analysis and visualisation (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, summer term) 2016: Project seminar Carpathians - seminar on sampling techniques and design (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 3 h, summer term) 2015: Applied Conservation Biology using R (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, module, 30 h, winter term) 2012: Spatial analysis and geostatistics (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 28 h, winter term) 2011 – 2018: Statistics I (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 28 h, winter term) 2011 – 2012: Introduction to Geoinformation processing (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 30 h, summer term) 2010: Ruhr Area and Geomatics (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, study trip, 4 days) 2010: Applied Geomatics (Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany, seminar, 28 h, summer term)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/skills/</guid>
      <description>Languages German (native), English (proficient), Spanish (basic)
Software ArcGIS, QGIS, R, SPSS, Python, GeoDa
Technical Data Harmonisation &amp;amp; Analysis, Geographic Information Systems (GIS), Machine Learning, Statistical Analyses</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>/home/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>